iprint.com 2015-06-23

# Business Cards, Custom Rubber Stamps, & Business Card Printing | iPrint

## Information Privacy

iPrint.com knows that you care about how information about you is used and shared, and we appreciate your trust that we will do so carefully and sensibly. This notice describes our Privacy Policy. By visiting iPrint.com, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy and in our Terms of Service found at www.iPrint.com.

The information we learn from customers helps us personalize and improve your shopping experience at iPrint.com. These are the types of information we gather:

### Information You Give Us

We store the information you enter when: you sign up for an account, place an order with us, or when you volunteer for other services. During this process you can choose whether or not you wish to receive information and specials via email from iPrint.com. We use this information for such purposes as responding to your requests, customizing future shopping for you, offering you promotions or specials for iPrint.com, improving our site, and communicating with you via email. If you change your mind and decide you do not wish to receive informational or promotional material via email in the future, or if you wish to correct or update any contact information you previously provided, please sign on to www.iPrint.com and make the changes under the "My Account" link. You may also follow the removal instructions at the bottom of each email message you receive from iPrint.com. Alternatively, you may let us know by sending an email to Customer_Service@iPrint.com. iPrint.com will not share your email address with any third parties, except our vendors who we contract with to deliver the services as specified by you.

### Automatic Information

We receive and store certain types of information whenever you interact with us. Like many Web sites, we use "cookies," to obtain certain types of information when your Web browser accesses iPrint.com. We utilize cookies to identify you as an iPrint.com customer, to recall your orders and to provide you with valuable features, such as pre-populating fields to reduce the amount of typing you do. We may also use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our service.

If you wish to control how your browser accepts cookies, the "help" portion of the toolbar on most browsers will tell you how to prevent your browser from accepting new cookies, how to have the browser notify you when you receive a new cookie, or how to disable cookies altogether. However, cookies allow you to take full advantage of some of iPrint.com's best features so it's beneficial to leave them turned on.

### Sharing of the Information

Information about our customers is an important asset of iPrint.com, which we value and protect. We will not share your email address with any third parties, except our vendors who we contract with to deliver the services as specified by you.

Although we use industry standard practices to protect your privacy, we do not promise, and you should not expect, that your personally identifiable information or private communications will always remain private. Due to the existing regulatory environment, we cannot ensure that all your private communications and other personally identifiable information will never be disclosed in ways not otherwise described in this Privacy Policy. For example, we may be forced to disclose information to the government under certain circumstances, or third parties may unlawfully intercept or access your private communications.

The following describes just some of the ways that your personally identifiable information may be disclosed:

**Vendors -** We employ other companies to perform functions on our behalf to fulfill orders, deliver packages, send postal mail and email, insert ads, analyze data, provide marketing assistance, provide additional product services, process credit card payments, and provide customer service. These vendors have access to certain personal information needed to perform their functions, but may not use your information for other purposes.

**Business Transfers -** As we continue to grow our business, we might sell or buy companies or assets. In such transactions, customer information generally is one of the transferred business assets. Also, in the event that iPrint.com or substantially all of its assets are acquired, or iPrint.com's Web business (www.iPrint.com) is acquired, customer information will be transferred.

**Protection of iPrint.com and Others -** We release account and other personal information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with law; enforce or apply our Terms of Service and other agreements; or protect the rights, property, or safety of iPrint.com, our users, or others. This may also include exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

### Notice

We may change this Privacy Policy from time to time based on your comments and our need to accurately reflect our data collection and disclosure practices. The use of information that we gather now is subject to the Privacy Policy in effect at the time of use. We may, but we shall not be required to, email you periodic reminders of our notices, unless you have instructed us not to, so you should check our Web site frequently to see recent changes.

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, our Terms of Service, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact:

> **iPrint.com**  
>  2435 Goodwin Lane  
>  New Braunfels, TX 78135  
>  (800) 238-6349
